================================================================
Andrea 0.3 - Designed by Lucian E. Marin | http://lucianmarin.com/
[Theme built for WordPress 2.5] 
[Licensed under GPL]
[June 3rd 2008]

How to install
-----------------

You should be looking at the Andrea folder right now if your reading this; if your not unzip the archive. You should than see a folder called andrea. 

Open up your FTP program and login to your server. Navigate to your WordPress folder and upload the entire folder (andrea) to your wp-content/themes folder.

Login to WordPress administration normally and select Presentation from the menu.

You should see a freshly installed theme called Andrea 0.3 and a few basic details about the theme. 

Active this theme by clicking Select on the right.

View your site to see The Journalist in all his glory. 
	
Note: A page refresh may be required.


Extra
-----------------

+Browser support
[I have tested The Journalist in the following browsers]

Firefox 1/2/3
Opera 8/9
Safari 2/3
Internet Explorer 6/7

+Credit
If you enjoy this theme please let me know; it only takes 5 minutes of your life. You can find details at: http://lucianmarin.com/


I hope you enjoy Andrea - Lucian E. Marin
================================================================